Guys, I'm going through something kinda hard.
伙计们 我最近过得有些不快活啊
Since Quinn and I broke up, she's gone back to dancing
自从Quinn和我分手后 她就又回到
at The Lusty Leopard, and it's just really tough because...
"欲望之豹"脱衣舞馆工作了 我太受不了了...
Cause you have to find a new strip club?
你得换家新的脱衣舞馆？
I have to find a new strip club!
我得换家新的脱衣舞馆！
I've been going to The Lusty Leopard for seven years.
七年了 "欲望之豹"一直是我的最爱
Wow. That's like 49 in perv years.
哇哦 对你这种色狼 就像过了49年了吧
Sixty-nine. Self-five.
69年 自己跟自己击掌
Look...
说实话...
without my open wallet,
没有我的慷慨解囊
The Lusty Leopard would be nothing.
"欲望之豹"没啥前途
Thanks to me, they've been able to expand
多亏了我 他们才可以扩张
and take over that soup kitchen next door.
盘下了隔壁的汤店
Now I'm a free agent,
现如今 我恢复自由身
and all the strip clubs are after me.
所有的脱衣舞馆都抢着要我
Mr. Stinson, we might not have
Stinson先生 我们"脱衣成金"
the best strippers at Moneyballs,
或许没有最好的脱衣舞娘
but we use sabermetrics to get you a stripper with a five body,
但是我们能用计量统计学 帮你找一个身材五分的
sure, and another with a butter face, but together,
还找一个背影杀手 让她们一起伺候您
with their tireless grinding, we guarantee
有她们无休止的缠绵挑逗
a high on-pants percentage.
老二"上座"率是保证的
I gotta be honest with you, Fred,
老实跟你说 Fred
I can't really see myself signing with the Golden Oldies.
我对你们"怀金岁月"的老女人真心没兴趣
Well, that's what everyone says... at first.
每个人都这么说... 当然是最开始
But our GILFs have got class.
但是我们的舞娘可是相当有水准的
They've got maturity and experience,
他们成熟 经验老道
and the kind of mind-blowing flexibility
而且骨骼惊奇 灵动如蛇
that only comes from advanced hip dysplasia.
绝对让你目瞪口呆
Barney, the Lusty Leopard would be lost without you.
Barney "欲望之豹"脱衣舞馆不能没有你啊
I think you're really gonna like a couple of the girls
我保证 你会喜欢从其他分馆里
we just pulled up from the minors.
挖过来的几个女娃子
Don't leave us!
求别走!
Wow, you're like the LeBron James of strip clubs.
哟 您可得是脱衣舞馆的"小皇帝"詹姆斯啊
Actually, you're probably tied with LeBron James for that title.
没准儿 你能和詹姆斯平起平坐呢
LeBron isn't all that.
"小皇帝"也没那么牛啊
The Cavs are doing great without him.
骑士队没他照样风生水起
Yeah!
是滴耶!
Hey, guys, you will never believe who I ran into
伙计们 你们猜猜今天在公司门口
outside of work today.
我碰到了谁
It wasn't the guy handing out coupons
不会是那个穿着热狗服
in the hot dog costume, was it?
发优惠券的那货吧?
Baby, there's no reason to be scared of him.
亲爱滴 不要害怕哈
I'm not scared of him.
我没害怕
It's totally normal to see a hot dog with a face.
热狗长脸 完全不稀奇嘛
No, it was Brad, my old law school buddy.
不 我碰到Brad了 我法学院的老同学
I almost didn't recognize him.
差点没认出来
Marshall?
Marshall不?
Brad?!
你是Brad?!
Bro!
哥们!
Oh, hey!
嘿!
What a kick-ass day!
今天太牛X了!
I run into you, some sucker throws away
我碰到了你 某个2货扔掉了
most of a perfectly good hot dog...
大半个巨好吃的热狗...
kick-ass day!
太牛X的一天了!
You still doing corporate law?
你还在搞法律这块么?
I got downsized two years ago.
我两年前就被裁员了
It's been rough.
一直过的不顺
Going through a little bit of a depresh.
有点小小失落啊
But just today, boom!
但是今天 爆棚了!
Huge job prospect.
超好的职业前景
Here's your application.
给 你的申请表
Just tell them I sent you.
告诉他们是我给你的
I bet you could fit in the bratwurst.
德国小香肠装肯定超配你
Bratwurst with a face.
长脸的德国小香肠
What'd I tell you?
我没骗你吧?
Looks like I'm about to be on a roll.
我要时来运转啦
Sounds like that guy could use some help.
貌似这哥们儿急需帮助啊
I know! That's why I said...
就是啊! 所我我才说...
You know, I'm at Honeywell & Cootes,
我现在在Honeywell & Cootes上班
and they're looking to hire an associate.
他们正在招一名助理律师
I could totally recommend you.
我完全可以推荐你
Leave the wounded behind!
人家还不够可怜吗!
老爸老妈浪漫史 第八季第七集
SCG 诚意出品
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组  http://hd.cnscg.com/ ==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: Uriana
翻译: 会唱歌的桨 发条橙 千欲 Uriana
校对: Uriana
Cause Brad is an old friend who needs a job.
Brad是老朋友了 正在找工作
Why shouldn't I give him
为什么我就不能
the old Marshall Eriksen Stamp of Approval?
给他"老Marshall的通力力荐"啊?!
Marshall, you're a stamp tramp.
Marshall 你是个"力荐废"
How dare you!
这你也说的出口!
And what is that?!
不过此话怎样?!
You give your stamp of approval to everything.
基本上什么东西你都会"力荐"
It's become meaningless.
这样就没意义了
It's like when my mom likes a movie.
就好像我妈喜欢一部电影
It just means Richard Dreyfuss is in it.
仅仅是因为Richard Dreyfuss出演了
Marshall, you love everything and everyone.
Marshall 你是一个老好人
It's... It's what I love about you,
这也是我爱你的地方
but it's also why your stamps are total crap.
但也是为什么你的"力荐"都是渣的原因
Give me one example.
举个例子
How about when you turned your boss
上次你把你老板搞得
into a fountain of bodily liquids?
吐到天翻地覆那件事怎么样?
You guys like it?
大伙儿还喜欢吗?
I'll be waiting for you in hell, Eriksen.
Eriksen 我们地狱见
In my defense, that restaurant's health rating had just gone
我要给自己说句话 那家餐馆的卫生等级
from an "F" to a "D," and I wanted to reward that.
才从F升到了D 我想要支持他们一下嘛
Marshall, you're already on thin ice
Marshall 你才在你老板面前
with that horrible Honeywell guy.
搞砸了一次
Don't risk screwing things up more right before
不要在接到你梦寐以求的大案子前
your biggest case ever.
把什么都搞砸了
Okay, Honeywell is not horrible,
好吧 Honeywell也没那么恐怖啊
he just has a bad temper sometimes.
他只是有时候脾气不大好
And he holds a grudge.
而且总爱记仇
He's kind of defensive about his height.
也不喜欢别人谈论他的身高
And he's cheap.
并且还很低贱
And he made those secretaries cry.
他还让那些秘书们伤心哭泣
But, deep down, he is a great guy.
但是 总的来说 他是个不错的人
Heck, he gets my stamp, too.
没错 他也是我的"力荐"了
Stamp tramp.
"力荐废"
Well, maybe this isn't the moment
好吧 或许现在不是你
to stick your neck out for Brad.
"力荐"Brad的好时候
Well, that's not how I was raised.
我所接受的教育可不是这样子
Back in St. Cloud, we believe in people,
在圣克劳德 我们对每个人都非常信任
people like Gudren Olsen, the town wino who became our mayor.
就像Gudren Olsen 那个后来当选我们市长的那个酒鬼
They even wound up naming a bridge after him.
他们甚至以他的名字命名了一座桥
The one he drove off.
不过他自个儿开车从那座桥上栽了下去
Marshall, why can't you be more like your wife?
Mshall 你怎么就不学学你老婆?
Lily's stamp is gold.
Lily"力荐"可是实打实的好货啊
I'm reading this book because of her.
因为她 我在读这本书
I'm drinking this beer because she recommended it.
因为她的推荐 我在喝这种啤酒
I'm even wearing this bra because
甚至我穿这款胸罩
of a lingerie store Lily told me about.
也是因为Lily告诉我了这家内衣店
Uh, if anyone's got the golden stamp,
如果谁的"力荐"是金字招牌的话
it's old Teddy Westside over here.
非我Ted莫属了
Please. You're a piggyback stamper.
得了吧 你就是个"力荐跟屁虫"
How dare you!
这话你也说得出口!
And what is that?!
不过此话怎讲?!
Allow us to demonstrate. Lily?
容我们来演示一番 Lily?
Hey, guys, I just found a great new sushi restaurant.
嘿 伙计们 我刚发现一家新的寿司店非常给力
It's called Katsu...
叫Katsu...
yoku. Katsuyoku.
yoku Katsuyoku馆
My ideas. I'm Ted.
是我Ted发现的
- Nailed it. - Totally.
- 搞定了  - 妥妥的
Okay, Ted, name one cool thing you've given
好吧  Ted 你就举个例子吧
- your stamp to first... - Dr. Berkowitz.
- 你什么时候有过原创...  - Berkowitz大夫
that isn't an ear, nose and throat doctor.
耳鼻喉医生不算
Man, these strip clubs want me so bad.
老天 那些脱衣舞馆对我日思夜想
They're sending me T-shirts, beer cozies.
送给我T恤 啤酒保温袋
Sticky's even sent me
"黏黏糖"那家甚至
a boob-shaped hand-sanitizer dispenser.
送给我个咪咪形的洗手液瓶
It's clean and dirty at the same time.
让我同时感觉到纯净和龌龊
That's it? T-shirts and beer cozies?
这就没啦? 只有T恤和啤酒保温袋?
That's disrespect, son!
奇耻大辱啊 小子!
Here's what you do:
你就该这样:
hit a few strip clubs in Jersey and Long Island.
去泽西和长岛混混脱衣舞馆
Jersey? Long Island?
泽西? 还长岛?
Why would I go to a Third World nation
为何我要跑去第三世界国家
to get my knob wobbled?
宠幸我的蛋蛋?
Well, you wouldn't.
哦 大可不必
But when the clubs in the city hear
不过当城里的俱乐部风闻
you're sniffing around across the river,
你在河对岸觅食时
those beer cozies and T-shirts turn
那些什么保温袋啊T恤啊
into Rolexes and fur coats.
马上就会升级成劳力士和皮大衣
Especially from that strip club, Fur Coats.
尤其是那家"貂皮大衣"舞馆
Wow. That's genius.
哇 这计划太天才了
You're hired.
大哥用你了
What do you mean?
什么意思?
I want you to be my strip club agent.
我要你做我的脱衣舞馆公关
What is wrong with you?
你脑子有毛病啊?
Well, I just figured I'd ask...
哦 我只是问问...
No, I was talking to myself,
不 我是在自言自语
because, for some reason, I really want to do that!
不知为何 这份差事让我心向往之!
Oh! Oh! What am I wearing?
哦! 哦！看我穿着什么啊?
Just proof of a stamp I know I gave first,
这就是我做过原创"力荐"的证明
from a little band called...
这个小乐队叫做...
Dishwalla.
Dishwalla乐队
Who?
哪位啊?
Dishwalla! Come on!
Dishwalla! 记得不!
They had that whole,
就是那首什么
"Tell Me All Your Thoughts on God" song.
"告诉我你怎么看上帝"的
Oh...
哦...
Look, I'm not saying they're my favorite band,
不是说我对这个乐队有多爱
but for a little while in college,
不过在大学有一段时间
we were all into that song, and it was all thanks to me.
我们都很喜欢这首歌 这都是我的功劳
But I turned you on to Dishwalla.
但是我让你们开始听Dishwalla的
No way! I played them on my radio show.
少来! 我还在自己的电台里播过他们的歌
I mean, pirate DJ Dr. X played them on
我是说 海盗DJ"X博士"在广受爱戴的
his beloved radio show.
电台节目上播过
We all know you were Dr. X, Ted!
我们都晓得你是"X博士"啦 Ted!
And I'm the one who got us into that song.
我才是让你们爱上那首歌的人
No! No! On his beloved radio show,
不是! 才怪! 在他大受欢迎
Dr. X pointed out that the chorus went,
的节目里 "X博士"说 歌里面唱到
"Tell me all your thoughts on God"
"告诉我你怎么看上帝"
"Cause I really want to meet her."
"因为我想和她见面"
" Her." God's a woman.
"她" 上帝是女人
And it blew the minds
这首歌让当晚收听
of everyone listening to Dr. X that night.
"X博士"节目的人耳目一新
Which was pretty much everyone on campus... including me.
我是指大学里的所有人... 也包括我哦
I'm not Dr. X.
我不是"X博士"
Oh, so you're saying
所以你是说
credit for the stamp goes to Dr. X then, not you.
这个"力荐"的功劳是"X博士"的不是你的啦
Okay... I'm gonna tell you guys something right now.
好吧... 我有些事情要告诉你们
Take a sip. Follow my lead.
喝一口 跟着我做
I'm Dr. X.
在下就是"X博士"
No!
真的假的!
I hope this works out, bro.
我希望事情能成 老哥
I couldn't even get my leg in that bratwurst outfit.
那套香肠服我连腿都塞不进去
Don't be nervous. Honeywell is gonna love you.
不要紧张 Honeywell会喜欢你的
Sweet! Freebie muff-tops!
好耶! 免费小松饼!
Can I pour you a pocket of coffee?
要不要我给你的口袋满上咖啡?
I didn't say you were fat.
我又不是说你肥
I said that dress makes you look fat! Idiot!
我是说那套衣服让你看起来大只! 傻帽!
Hey! You must be Brad!
嘿! 你一定就是Brad了!
I'm excited to meet the man
能见到本人我真是兴奋啊
Eriksen's been talking up all week.
Eriksen都已经念叨了一星期了
Mr. Honeywell, I have to say,
Honeywell先生 我不得不夸一句
your environmental work is amazing.
你这的环保工作真是让人叹为观止
Come on, it's not like I'm saving the world.
少来 好像我多了不起似的
Oh, wait, yes, I am!
哦 等下 我是了不起哦!
Great.
好的
Marshall tells me you have
Marshall告诉我
the big Gruber Pharmaceutical trial coming up.
你就要办"Gruber制药"的大案子
I'd love to give you my thoughts on the case,
我想就这个案子提点建议
but I can't take full credit.
但不全是我的功劳喔
Most of these are from my psychic.
这些大多是我的通灵师给的
My psychic always
我的通灵师
pushes for a settlement.
老是急着下定论
But my numerologist says roll the dice with the jury.
但是那个命理师说陪审团的事情就随缘
I'm waiting for my astrologist to weigh in,
我正等着我的占卜师也提供点意见
but he can be kind of flaky.
不过他这人有点古怪
You know, Cancer.
得癌的都这样
Should know more after he's back from chemo.
等他做完化疗之后会给我消息
Good luck, bro!
好运哦 老哥!
You know the best part about you challenging me on Dishwalla?
知道你跟我叫板Dishwalla这件事情为啥好吗?
- Didn't challenge you, don't care. - It made me
- 没跟你叫板 压根不在乎  - 我把
dig up my old video diaries from freshman year.
大学第一年的录像日记找了出来
And somewhere in here there's gonna be proof
这些录像带就可以证明
that I am not a piggyback stamper.
我的"力荐"不都是跟屁虫
I have my own original ideas.
我自有原创的点子
Didn't you only do the video diaries
你做录像日记不是因为
because of Winona Ryder in Reality Bites?
Winona Ryder演的"四个毕业生"吗?
No.
不是
I don't know what you're talk... shut up.
我才不知道你说什么... 闭嘴啦
Let's just watch.
我们就看吧
How do you even know there's gonna be mention
你怎么知道带子上会提到
- of Dishwalla on those tapes?  - I don't.
- Dishwalla这档子事  - 我不知道
And it may take me days to go through them all,
把这些看上一遍可能要花上我几天
but that is how committed I am to the truth.
但这正说明我对真相的执着
Hey, you guys should check out that song by the band Dishwalla.
嘿 你们应该听听那个叫Dishwalla的乐队的歌
Really? I've never heard of them.
真的? 我没听过他们
Damn it!
妹的!
So?
所以?
Bottom line, Vito， a lot of
这已经是底线了 Vito
strip clubs are into my client.
很多脱衣舞馆都要我的客户
If you want the Melon Patch to be in the mix,
如果你希望"瓜罩"馆位列其中
we're gonna need bigger melons and smaller patches.
那些"瓜"就得大点 "罩"就得小一点
Otherwise, your establishment is not where
如若不然 Barney Stinson
Barney Stinson is gonna pitch his tent.
要怎么进驻你的小店
B-Dawg, Barn Door,
B兄 Barn哥
Stinson-natti, Bro-hio!
Stinson 我哥们!
Talk to me. How's it hangin'?
跟我说说 最近如何啊?
You are killing it at this agent thing!
当公关你是万夫莫敌啊!
I just got a big box at Yankee Stadium
我刚刚拿到了洋基队比赛的包厢票
from the ladies at The Big Box.
"盒中女"馆给我送来的
Mm-hmm.
嗯
One question: Golden Oldies
有个问题: "怀金岁月"馆
just sent me a fax machine and a Charo calendar.
刚给我送来了传真机和老明星挂历
- Mm-hmm.  - Aren't they out of the running?
- 嗯?  - 不是都停产了吗?
Yeah, but those old bitches don't need to know that.
是啊 但这些老婊不用知道啦
Yeah, I just feel kind of bad.
嗯 我感觉自己坏坏的
They just spent eight grand
他们花了八千大洋
on that wheelchair ramp up to the stage.
在台上打了个轮椅通道
Hey, Larry, how's everything at the Beaver Dam?
嘿 Larry "比佛丹"那边如何?
I don't even know that strip club.
怎么我都没听过这个脱衣舞馆
Oh, it's not a club.
这不是那种地方
My cousin Larry is a forest ranger in Squamish.
我表弟Larry是Squamish那的护林人员
Oh, yeah?
是吗?
Then I was fired from Bed Bath & Beyond
然后我就被家具店炒了
for telling inappropriate jokes.
因为一个玩笑开过头了
I mean...
我想说...
get a sense of humor, La Shonda.
La Shonda 别那么没趣
You know how "they" are.
"那些人"你懂的
"They" meaning Bed Bath & Beyond employees, right?
"那些人"是说家具店的人 对吗?
No. Women.
不对 是那些女的
That still could have been worse.
还能更糟
Thank God I ran into Marshall.
感谢老天让我碰到Marshall了
This guy's supportive as balls.
他就像那活一样 挺我到现在
And here I am.
然后我就过来了
Yes, we both owe Marshall a debt of gratitude
是啊 能让您这种人来面试
for getting you this interview.
我还真得好好感谢Marshall
Eriksen...
那Eriksen...
- Can I see you outside?  - Sure.
- 我们来外面谈一会?  - 好的
Good. Try to stay out there a few minutes.
好的 尽量在外面多待一会
I just cut one, and I can tell it's gonna be a slow burn.
我一直忍着屁 而且我保证会绵长悠远
What is Generation X?
什么是X世代?
What does the X in "Generation X" stand for?
"X世代"中的X所代表什么意思?
What do we stand for?
我们又是什么?
Why aren't people on campus talking about this?
为什么学校里的人从来不去讨论这些?
Maybe you should do a radio show
也许你该搞个电台秀
and call yourself Dr. X.
自称"X博士"
I just had an amazing idea.
我的灵感来了
Just turn it off!
关掉别看了!
I can't look away.
我无法不看
Oh, God, no.
哦不 别
Oh, God, I'm putting on a beret.
老天 我居然戴个贝雷帽
You were there.
你也在那
Why didn't you tell me that looked stupid?
你为什么不提醒我这样子很傻?
"Ted, that beret looks stupid."
"Ted 你戴这帽子很傻"
"I agree to disagree."
"咱俩求同存异"
Marshall, that man is the human equivalent of what came out
Marshall 这家伙比你上次推荐的
of my body after eating that soup you recommended!
那种汤还要让人恶心!
This guy's your friend?
这家伙是你朋友?
Really more of an acquaintance than a friend.
只是比较熟悉的陌生人罢了
No backpedaling.
不要退缩
You're Marshall Eriksen.
你是Marshall Eriksen
You believe in people.
要对别人有信心
You know what Brad hasn't told you?
你知道Brad有些事儿没说吗?
He was third in our class at Columbia.
他是哥伦比亚大学我们班上的第三名
That is impressive.
确实不错
And I suppose he did warn us about the fart.
而且他放屁之前还好意地提醒了我们
He's a great guy.
他人很不错
Please... give him just one more chance.
求你了... 再给他一次机会吧
Two more minutes.
顶多再谈两分钟
I'm proud of you.
我以你为荣
I'm proud of you for being proud of me.
我以你以我为荣为荣
You went undergrad to Holy Cross?
你是在圣十字学院毕业的?
That's my alma mater.
那是我的母校
I went there on a basketball scholarship.
我在那是篮球特长生
No way. I played center.
不会吧 我也当过中锋
Why is that so shocking?
你干嘛那样?
'Cause you're, like, an itty-bitty fella.
因为你 那个 像个小不点
Hey, uh, fish, huh?
嘿 呃 这是鱼 对吧?
Fish are crazy, right?
这些鱼很好玩 对吧?
You guys ever think about fish?
你们想过这些鱼吗?
I am six-foot one, sir.
我有一米八五 先生
Bro, I'm at least a foot taller than you.
老兄 我至少高你三十公分
Well, then I guess that makes you a freakish seven-foot one.
那你就是畸形 两米多的畸形
What do you call fish with no eyes?
没有眼睛的鱼叫啥?
"Fsh."
"嘘"(Fish少个i)
I am six-feet and one inch, and I'll prove it.
我是一米八五 我来证明给你看
Eriksen.
Eriksen 过来
How tall are you?
你有多高?
Seven feet.
两米一三(其实只有一米九)
So, we've got a deal somewhere?
那 决定好了去哪了吗?
We sure do.
当然了
You are the new face of...
恭喜你加入...
and exclusive customer to...
还是贵宾喔...
Golden Oldies!
"怀金岁月"!
What?!
神马?!
I thought we ruled them out!
我们不是排除了那吗!
I don't remember that!
我怎么不记得!
Now let's go. It is 4:00,
那咱走吧 现在是4点整
and their dinner show starts in ten minutes.
晚场秀10分钟以后就开始了
Wait a minute.
等一下
Is that a Rolex?
这是劳力士吗?
Huh. What do you know?
你怎么发现的?
How did that get there?
什么时候戴我手上的?
Anyway, uh, so initial here and...
总之 这儿签字...
Where'd you get the bling, Robin?
哪儿来的珠宝项链 Robin?
They bribed you.
他们收买你了
They bribed you!
他们贿赂你!
Why else would you pick a place where the strippers say
要不然你为啥选这地方
they're trying to put their grandkids through college?!
尽是些供她们孙子上大学的舞娘?!
Please leave!
你走吧!
Barney, I can explain, okay?
Barney 你听我解释 行吗?
Please...
请...
leave.
走
Say it, you giant beast! Say I'm six-one!
说啊 你这个大怪兽! 说我有一米八五!
Maybe if you stood on top of that pot of gold
可能你踩在彩虹上
you have at the end of your rainbow.
能有一米八五吧
You know something?!
你知道吗?!
You're nothing but a...
你只是一个...
a tree man!
一个傻大个!
I never want to see you again, tree man!
我再也不想在我这儿看到你 傻大个!
Fine.
好啊
I have to go to the little boys' room.
那我得去一个小房间
Not your office.
我不是说你房间
I need to take a dump.
我要蹲坑
If that's the type of guy you vouch for,
如果你连这种人都推荐
I can't trust your judgment.
那我再也不能相信你了
You're off the Gruber Pharmaceutical case.
"Gruber制药"的案子不要你了
No...
不...
Oh, good, we're up to the time I got my ear pierced.
好极了 快到我耳朵上打洞的情节了
Do it, do it.
快啊 快啊
Don't do it! Don't do it! Don't, don't.
不 我不行! 不能这么做! 不行 不行
Okay, do it now. Do, do, do it, do it.
好了 就是现在 下手 开始了
Don't, don't do it! Don't do it! Don't do it!
不行 不能这么做! 不行! 不行!
Don't! Yes, you can do this. You can...
不行! 行 你行的 你能...
That goes on for 45 minutes.
一直纠结了45分钟
Hey... how was work, baby?
嘿... 工作如何 亲爱的?
Remember how I always wanted to know
你记得我总想变成鬼魂
what it was like to be a ghost?
感觉一下吗?
Well, I don't want that anymore.
我再也不想受这种罪了
Okay, suppose we lead
好吧 如果我们以
with the carbon testing of the residue water.
废水的碳含量检测开头的话
How do we keep the jury engaged? Anyone?
如何往下接呢? 谁有点子?
You could bring up the survey from
可以呈上对Pasquesi博士
Dr. Pasquesi's testimony.
那份证词的分析
Anyone?
谁有点子?
Anyone who isn't dead to me?
除了死人 谁有点子?
Then you have to earn Honeywell's trust back.
你要赢回Honeywell的信任
Just start small.
从点滴做起
Put your stamp on little things
从那些无关工作的事
that have nothing to do with work.
开始"力荐"
Like a funny video.
比如说搞笑视频
I, uh, I may have something.
我 呃 能提供
Don't think, Mosby! Do it now! Oh, my God, I'm doing it!
别犹豫 Mosby! 下手吧! 喔天呐 我下手了!
Wow, he's a real bleeder!
他可真能捣鼓!
And then you build to something else small, like a tasty snack.
然后延伸到其他小事 比如美味小吃
Don't sleep on the popcorn.
别抱着爆米花睡觉喔
Try mixing the caramel and the cheese.
试试焦糖味和芝士味混搭
It shouldn't work,
很奇怪的组合
but... it... does.
却很... 好... 吃
There's no way caramel and cheese... That's good!
焦糖和芝士怎么可能... 太棒了!
That is good. Oh!
真心好吃 喔!
And when Honeywell starts trusting your stamp again,
等到Honeywell再次相信你的"力荐"之后
he'll seek out your opinion on things.
他就会寻求你的建议
Be honest, Eriksen.
说实话 Eriksen
Is this deep-V working?
深V领适合我吗?
And that's when you lie your ass off.
这时候 天花乱坠地吹吧
Sir...
先生...
I think you could go even deeper.
领子还能更深点
And before you know it...
不知不觉...
Eriksen, get in here.
Eriksen 进来
you're back on the case.
你继续跟进这个案子了
Ted, why are you torturing yourself?
Ted 何必这样自虐呢?
None of us were our best in college.
谁在大学都不是完美的
Oh, my God, I love my hair there!
天呐 当年我头发真好看!
I always thought I was this kid from suburban Ohio
我总觉得我是个Ohio郊区的孩子
who had this innate sense of judgment and taste
天生有独特的看法和品味
and just showed up to college and wowed everyone.
进大学后 大家都为我倾倒
Now I have concrete proof that I wasn't.
现在 我能肯定我不是了
I was a total gomer.
我就是个古董
Maybe I still am.
可能现在也是
Wait... that's the giant suit
等等... 那是Marshall
Marshall wore on our third date.
和我第三次约会穿的大西装
So...
那...
Marshall Eriksen,
Marshall Eriksen先生
you just came back from your third date with Lily.
你刚从和Lily的第三次约会回来
How was it?
感觉如何?
Great, yeah.
很棒
I just... I think I'm falling for this girl pretty hard.
我... 我觉得我对这女孩深深着迷了
But is everything happening too fast?
是不是发生得太快了?
I mean, maybe I should see other people.
也许 我可以再约点别的女生
Whoa, dude, no!
喂 哥 别啊!
Lily Aldrin is special. You hold on to that girl.
Lily Aldrin很特别 你好好待她
She is.
确实
I'm only 18 and...
可我才18岁...
Marshall, you being 18 isn't a bad thing.
Marshall 18岁并不是坏事
It just means you get to spend even more of your life with her.
这意味着你们这辈子有更多时间在一起
I mean, I'm probably not gonna meet my wife
你看 等我找到我老婆
until I'm, like, 23.
那都可能 23岁了
You're right.
你说得对
What am I thinking?
我胡思乱想什么呢?
I'm in love with this girl.
我爱这女孩
Ted, oh, my God.
Ted 天呐
You gave me the ultimate stamp.
你给了我"终极力荐"
And in my whole life, this life...
我这辈子 此生...
it all goes back to that moment.
都由那一刻决定了
I mean, maybe take a month off, bang a couple chicks.
不过可以缓一个月 上几个妹子
Lily's not going anywhere.
反正Lily跑不掉
- Hey, Barney.  - Hey.
- 嘿 Barney  - 嘿
Um, look, I'm sorry about the whole skimming-off-the-top-
对"拿脱衣舞馆的手短"这事
of-the-strip-club-swag thing.
我很抱歉
Hey, it happens to everybody.
嘿 谁都有过的
Really? Because even as I said those words,
真的? 就算我说得这么正经
they did not feel like a real thing.
也听起来一点不正经啊
Hey, look, wherever you end up, can I have the dubious honor
嘿 不管你最终决定去哪 能否给我个机会
of buying you your first lap dance?
给你买第一场膝上舞?
It's a date.
那说定了
Ladies and gentlemen, it's time for "The Decision."
女士们先生们 现在是"决定一刻"
Yeah.
是的
Ladies, my bro-dium?
女士们 我的哥台呢?
Yeah.
不错
Look at this!
看啊看啊!
Man, this whole free agent experience,
诸位 这段自由脱衣客经历
it's been an unbelievable experience,
我认为十分美好
a real humbling experience.
自身学到很多
First of all, The Lusty Leopard is where I developed my game.
首先 我要感谢"欲望之豹" 我的老东家
Oh...
噢...
I have nothing but the utmost respect for you skanks.
我对妹子们表示由衷的敬佩
He's just gonna stay at The Lusty Leopard.
他会留在"欲望之豹"的
They have loyalty and heart.
他们又忠诚 又有心
I bet you he rewards that.
他会感激这点的
LeBron moved on, Ted. So should you.
詹姆斯向前看了 Ted 你也别墨迹
But Barney Stinson has to do what's right
但Barney Stinson必须做出对的决定
for Barney Stinson's penis.
为了我深爱的老二
In this fall... This is tough.
这个脱衣季... 艰难的决定
In this fall I'm going
这个脱衣季 我将
to take my talents to Mouth Beach.
让Mouth Beach为我效劳
The next day, Uncle Marshall went to court
第二天 Marshall叔去了法庭
for the biggest case of his life.
他这辈子跟过最大的案子
Hey, Marshall! Bilbo!
嘿Marshall! Bilbo!
Brad? What are you...?
Brad? 你怎么...?
Did you just get hired
你怎么突然被
by Gruber Pharmaceutical's legal team?
"Gruber制药"律师团雇了?
Oh, not just.
不是突然
I've been working for them for two years.
为他们工作两年了
I heard about the job opening at Honeywell & Cootes
我听说你们Honeywell & Cootes在招人
and knew that if I hung out in front of your office
料到我在你公司楼下转悠
and pretended to be down on my luck, you'd take pity on me,
扮成落汤鸡模样 你就会可怜我
get me an interview...
让我去面试...
Try to stay out there a few minutes.
尽量在外面多待一会
I just cut one, and I can tell it's gonna be a slow burn.
我一直忍着屁 而且我保证会绵长悠远
and buy some alone time in the conference room.
我独自在你们会议室待了一会
I got your firm's strategy for the case.
你们公司的计划我全知道了
Muchas gracias, bro-migo.
多谢你啦 好哥们
He's really more of an acquaintance than a bro-migo.
什么好哥们 更像是点头之交
Win this case or you're fired, Eriksen.
输了案子你就被开除了 Eriksen
And so began the trial that would change the course
也就是这场法庭审判 成为了Marshall
of Marshall's career.
事业的转折点
But we'll get to that.
这个以后再说
Oh, you see?! This is what I miss about being single:
懂了不?! 这就是我为什么怀念单身:
cutting loose at a strip club,
在脱衣舞馆放纵
drinkin' some beers, seein' some boobs,
喝点啤酒 看点胸
getting thrown out for being "too handsy."
"咸猪手"被扔出来
You were a little out of control tonight.
你今晚有点失控
You know, I really thought
知道么 我真以为
that that bouncer was bluffing with the Taser.
那保镖拿电击枪是唬人的
Man, everything's gonna taste like pennies for a week.
今晚之后 一周不知肉味啊
I had a fun time tonight, though.
不过我今晚玩得很开心
Me, too.
我也是
I always have fun with you.
和你在一起总是很开心
Whoa, whoa.
哇 哇
I... I've got to... um...
我... 我得... 呃...
We can't, we can't do this.
我们 不能这样
This, this can't happen.
这 不能发生
- Uh, I've got to go.  - What...?
- 呃 我要走了  - 什么...?
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组  http://hd.cnscg.com/ ==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: Uriana
翻译: 会唱歌的桨 发条橙 千欲 Uriana
校对: Uriana